okay switch back so there's the new one featured very cool okay so you can bookmark this later but
you just add the word admin to the end of the url it'll be your url this is the test site so and
then i can set up a specific login for you so yeah we're just going to look at all of this stuff
really quickly the main page is products of course we have live drafts sold archived and all the
little eyeball is to preview it and then archives to archive it so once we'll archive that ducky one
and speedo when you have orders that haven't been looked at yet it will be flashing and then it'll
always show how many unfulfilled orders there are so there's one right now show you how to do a
refund the way that stripe works is it allows you to refund any amount that you want so basically
we set it up so that you can add the amounts so you wanted to add both of those and you don't
have to relist both of them we'll relist both of them and then let's say we're keeping 100 bucks
for a restocking fee uh so i dropped it down
to 300 and then that way you can refund it and it will go through stripe and refund them
all of their purchase minus the hundred dollars that you kept